

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Working as a Consultant seeking roles in IT Support, Job scheduling tool Autosys, Application Support, Production Support, Incident Management, Project Management, Root Cause Analysis, Requirement Gathering, SQL Server, Autosys, Unix & ITIL.



Current Designation: Consultant Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Ciber Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Chennai Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical]

Pref. Location: Chennai, Hyderabad, Bengaluru / Bangalore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Tech Support Engnr

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Associate Consultant, Tech Support Engineer, IT Support, Application Support, Production Support, Desktop Support, Incident Management, Project Management, Root Cause Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Systems

Administration, Client Servicing, SQL Server, Autosys

Verified : Chone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

### Summary

Having a total of 4.5 years of IT experience in various banking and financial sectors and capital marketing. Technologies handled in the tenure of my IT period Different Job scheduler's AutoSys & Control-M, various Unix and Linux operating systems. Good knowledge in ITIL Process.

## **Work Experience**

Ciber as Consultant Nov 2019 to Till Date

Expertise in Autosys job scheduling and create, update or delete jobs/machines using JIL, provide interactive access, support job scheduling changes (Calendar updates, password update, perform send event commands in PRD /QA environment) based on the request from DEV team.

Monitor production jobs to ensure successful execution as scheduled and assist in troubleshooting of failed processes or jobs for root cause analysis. Incident and change ticket management which include break fix in AutoSys, job promotions, administering/controlling the jobs through command line interface.

Jobs health check. Supporting GL Archive

Monitor research analyze and report problems to programmer or PDO Teams. Maintaining the shift turnover, which includes the current and the pending information from one shift to another

Build and manage job flows, calendar requirement and scheduling criteria.

Capgemini as Associate Consultant

Oct 2018 to Jun 2019

Incident and change ticket management which include break fix in Control M, job promotions, administering/controlling the jobs through command line interface. Jobs health check.

Triggering SQL queries through MS SQL server 2014.

Checking the agent health checks

Monitor research analyze and report problems to programmer or developer.

Maintaining the shift turnover, which includes the current and the pending information from one shift to another

Build and manage job flows, calendar requirement and scheduling criteria

Syntel pvt Ltd as Associate Consultant Feb 2016 to Sep 2018

Incident management in Autosys which include the support for failure or

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. hung jobs.

Scheduling and promoting the jobs following the standard ITIL process. Communicating with business heads and application managers during the issues with jobs triggering or for long running jobs.

Manual copy of files from source to destination as a part of break fix of

Autosys issues using scp and sftp commands

Supporting Eagle Pace Application for End-to-End Business integration as

Involving the various support teams at time of severe issues.

As it is an enhancement project, we usually interact with client over phone/e-mail/SFB frequently.

Monitoring/controlling production and test automated processes and working closely with the Systems Administration team to identify areas for

improvement or possible automation

Providing first/second level support to end-users as needed

System problem research and resolution.

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2012

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Autosys.WCC, Unix	R11,R11.4.	2021	3 Year(s) 7 Month(s)
SQL Server,	2014	2017	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				
Tamil				

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

# **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

 ${\it Careers-About\, Us-Clients-Terms\,\&\, Conditions-FAQ's-Contact\, Us-Report\, a\, Problem-Site\, Map-Resources}$ Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.